{
    "id": "ba900543864d417b9d5f7b303b4d532f",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can you see a woman ............................... the picture?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46f02211d7b549cca0b35f4f7d10a242"
        },
        {
            "question": "London is ............................... the river Thames.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c756f4f5a144ad1a2b022f5c91d2085"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man is sitting ................................. a table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "in front of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "557e54cd3896411f9ad13070e0a72b60"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother sat ................................ her children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3776e0f80a384716a395d1475f6e7062"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are a laptop and a few books ............................... the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7a04971afe445fab4257f46384f8ff3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He put the money ..................................... the box.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8913a7bbefeb42dcbd033daed597ee1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat was hiding .................................. the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "behind",
                "out",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2de1f92667934e8385b0141eab5a8480"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do you wear that ring ................................... your first finger?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc25a39eea4d4319b68e946aa034de53"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you see the helicopter ..................................... the palace?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e89c5818ecb4057852754b6f4c8b64b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plane was flying ................................. Scotland.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d716ad8b2904a2689cebdd9ca0b48c5"
        }
    ]
}